Hello everyone, in this section, I will guide you to practice the basic steps in finding Delta using the GTX Automation tool.
First, I will open this tool.
At the main interface, I will go to Analytics Support, select Check Delta from Database, Save Point.
Here I will have the fields where I will fill in the necessary information for me to be able to operate.
The first is Analyze Parts.
Here I will save the part file of the file that contains the modules I need to analyze.
In this step, I will have two options.
The first option is to use File Analysis.
This File Analysis is the result of the analysis.
The second option is to use the report file generated from the TPA Report Generation tool.
It contains a lot of modules.
Testing Team uses this file for the analysis.
For the use of a small number of modules, I will choose Option 2.
Here I will have a template file that I will fill in the basic information of the module I need to analyze.
Then I will input the part of that file into this.
Now I will demo the first option, which I will input the part of the analysis.
In this case, I have a Part Analyze Seed like this, generated from the TPA Report Generation tool.
Here we have a lot of modules, many components, including the modules that have been tested and have not been tested.
Then I will consider which modules that have mtvdict and undefined here
Then I will support me to analyze those modules
Then I will copy the part of this file I input into my first field
The second part is the part of the database
This is the part of the folder in front of the database
I load with snapshots or streams using CCC about my local
Here I will have the database here
I will copy this part and input into the tool here
Next, I will create a folder
Here I will create folder workspace 1
This folder will contain the files and documents generated in my tool process
Here I have created the folder workspace 1 in front of it
At the same time, I also put the file analysis into this folder
I will copy the part of this folder
Next is the switch setting part
This is the part of the CSV file generated in the build config process using CCC
Then I will go to the database
Go to GEN
Select the corresponding config
Then select BUILD
And I will take the part of this file switchsetting.csv
Then I will select this part
Next, I will adjust this parallel thread
Here I will have an maximum of 8 threads
By selecting the corresponding number, I will help this tool to work faster
It corresponds to the number of this tool running in a row
At the development tool, they define the maximum of 8 threads
Here I choose the maximum value of 8
Then click Create data file
Here my data can be used to run the program
Click Create data file
Here's the result after running the program
This is the result after running the first step
Here I will have 3 types of my module
I will have All, All, NoCode and New
The result is also shown here
Each with New, All and NoCode
Each with the number 28, each with New
16 is All and 8 is NoCode
I can observe the running process of Tune
I can open Terminal here
To easily observe, I can divide the window into 2 parts
To see the details of which module belongs to which teacher
I will go to Folderwork Space I just created
Then I will go to Output
And select Open Modules Input
Then I will go to Format
Here I will have all the modules
That are listed here
I will have New Modules
European Modules
And the rest is All and NoCode
With the current type, the New Modules
Are the modules that haven't been test-tripped
In the database
I have logged back from Stream
It will be listed as New
And the old modules here
Are the modules that have been test-tripped
That have been tested in the previous version
In the existing database
Tune will be listed as All
And the old and NoCode modules
Are the modules that have the TPA file
That are NoCode
That have been tested before are All and NoCode
Here Tune will help me
To list these modules
As All and NoCode
Then I will test this file
First, I will solve the first modules
As All
In here, I choose All
Here I will have 16
Modules as All
Next, I will click Create Folder
Then we will create the text folder for these modules
After step 1, there is a window to start the creation of the text folder
Then, we will go to the next step, which is the build text
Here, the tool will help you build the text folders
with the corresponding test script that has been copied from the database
After going to the Steps row, I will report the result for me here
The code has been automatically collected for the module
To see the detailed results
I go to Find Module Info
Here I will have the detailed results
I will have the following data
The first is Success
The second is Fall
The third is Fail
The first is Success
Then I will have one
Sequential module
Success
The results are 0, 0, 0, 0, 0.
And here I can find that the module has been failed
I will have the module failed here
I will sort out this failed module in the next steps
I will look at these files
And for the failed modules, I will use Tool Support to go to the Tool Defined Objects and click on this button for the 15 failed modules.
In this step, Tool will support me to find the missing objects in the header file of the test-trips copied from the database to the folder I have just created.
Here I can also see the number of modules that have been copied.
And here I can also see the number of modules that have been copied.
After going to file object, we will have status
Successful is 14
Fail is 1
Total is 15
Then we will go to repair guest suite for failed modules
Thanks for watching
After this step, the result will appear in this box, I will have successful is 15, failed is 0, and my total is 15 that I have.
Then I will go through the review step, failed module, to get result for the modules I have just finished.
Don't forget to subscribe for more video.
Thank you and take care.
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
After finishing the review of the failed module, here I will have 11 successful modules, 4 modules that have been failed in total 15 modules of mine
To see the details, I will open the module info file here
At the beginning, I only had 1 successful module and 15 modules that had been failed
Now I only have 1 successful module and 15 modules that had been failed
In total we have 12 successful modules with the results of C0, C1, and MCTc game
Of those, we still have 4 modules failed
So now that we have a number of module out, we are going to come to the newly installed modules
Now, in this new module, there is no test script for those modules that have been tested in the previous version.
I will find on a database called Xeboy and store the test scripts I have tested for these modules in the previous version
on other projects, or other versions, or in other projects, or in other streams, or in other snapshots.
I will find on Xeboy.
I will test this file.
In Xeboy's information,
I will have
the
Xeboy link.
I will input the Xeboy link that contains the test scripts that have been completed for my previous tasks.
This is Xeboy on the side of the UT team.
I will have
the folders
containing the tests.
Here I will have the
folder of TeX environment in.
Here I will have the Puesi
right there.
the data excessive In the TeX environment folder I will save all the test scripts I have tested for those modules.
Then, among the various modules in the TeX environment.
then I will take the
data from the server to the database, then I will put it in the tool here
and then I will load the database, then I will choose trainer or challenge,
then the reason I want, here I will have the custom check,
because right now I'm demoing
the control check of the DMC, then I will choose the phone number 6 is the DMC
to analyze the new module, here is the data type, then I will choose the new
here I will have two options, the first option is I will search each module separately
in this section I will have to fill in the information as the name module
and then I will have to fill in the information as the name module
so I can find it and I will be able to search for that module or I can choose to search for the new module
here I will choose all of the modules instead of new, they will list information for me once
I will definitely choose the first module
here I will have the new module and I will choose another module here
then I will choose the second module, then I will search for the new module here
After that, I will input the name of that module into the oModuleName
After that, I will click Search
File
Now you can see the related information
Everything is good
After completing this step, I see that there are 4 tests completed in that module.
In that module, the test environment is test, the name of the stream and the snapshot, as well as the pp number are displayed in these 3 columns.
Now I will choose a test that I chose to refer to the current module.
I will choose this one.
If I want to download the test script, I will create a folder.
Here I created a sample folder here.
In this folder, I will copy the silver folder.
Then I will click the right mouse button to enter the test that I want to download.
Then I will select the download folder.
In the CMA folder, I will see that the new folder is created for my newly downloaded module.
Then I will build test for that module.
After that, to see the details, I will open the module info file here.
Then I will see that the module I just chose to download the test delta back.
Then I will see that the module I just choose to download the test delta back.
.
After that, I will define the missing object in the new module.
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
After that, I will go to the next step, Repair, Get Suits
As you can see, the result I have here is SuccessfullyLineName
After that, I will go to the next step, RebuildFileModule to get the result of the red module
Then
After that I will open Module Enforced
And here it is
For the moment, it's turned into a Success
Go back to X不好 share Oak
Thanks for watching
cdc, and this one. After looking at all the steps, now I will see that I still have 4
modules that have failed, then I can select all the delta tested items that have been
tested in this way. Then I will download the test strips in the previous version of those
modules and build them again to see the results in this file.
So here I have finished the demo for everyone about the first option in the case of
Analyze, I input the information of the Analyze file here.
After this step, I will demo for everyone how to use a module list file.
Then I will open this file.
To use another file, here I will create another workspace folder, I will call it
workspace2.
Here I will have a file called module list file.
Here I will have a switch called merge report.
Here I will define the columns that still fill in the information to provide the information
that the tool can use.
Haha.
Then you can see the Instruction here, the yellow bars are the bars in front of the information that have to be filled, and the blue bars are the optional ones.
Or you can see the information in the Seed Sample so you can see the format of the data that needs to be filled.
In this file, the data that needs to be analyzed will be in SeedMatchReport.
Currently, I will have a list of the components listed here.
I will use this file to analyze the modules that need to find data.
I will copy this list.
Copy
the white file of this file.
Then I will input it into the Analyze bar.
Then I will use the old database here.
The database I will input is database number 2.
And the switch setting, I will use the switch setting as before.
Here I will not change the switch setting.
Then I will click on Create Data File.
Here I will see the information.
After running, I will have two modules.
One is New and the other is Old.
You can see here.
You can see that the information is currently here.
New Old and Old Code.
Then I will have New is 4, Old is 10.
To see the information in detail, I will go to the Output folder.
I will open the Info module file here.
Then I will see that there are 4 New modules and the remaining number is Old.
It corresponds to 10 modules here.
So I will copy the original code here.
Press Enter to open it.
To see the information, I will go to the dialog box of the new module.
Then I will open the Info module, into the command bar,
I will enter the name of the new module here.
In this module, you will see that the new module is Old.
You can see that there are 5 modules here.
And the last one is New.
Then it will include the Create Delta File, Create Folder, and also the Build Test for me
At this point, I will choose O, so that the Build Test will build the O module for me
The Build Test will start at 3 o'clock
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
After completed holographic step
Let's see the our step
In this info module file, I will have a failed module and 9 successful modules with the results of C0, C1, and MCDC.
I will have 4 new modules here.
Next, I will manage these new modules.
In the old time delta, I will switch to new.
Then I will select the relevant information in the information section.
In this step, I will demo the search new module.
That is, I will search all the modules that have the name new listed in the Excel file just now.
So I have 4 modules that need to search delta on Savoy.
While waiting for iTunes to run, I will create a folder to download the scripts on Savoy.
I have created a folder like this.
Then I will copy and paste the part of that folder.
After running, I will see that there are 4 modules to search.
I found that there are test scripts on Savoy.
Then I will copy and paste the part of that folder on Savoy.
After that, here I will have the modules that are test by delta and test.
Then I will choose the modules that have the test environment by delta.
Then I will choose this one.
Next up is this section...
Then I'm going to...
... download these two back.
Then I will choose create folder for these two modules
I will go to folder to check it again
Next is this old module
I will build this module
I test for this module
After complete from build test
I will
chek to see what happened
I will go to Inner Boolean
Notice that recently installed module is already Bfell
I can use AutoDefault Object to show it
order Bfell can take a year
Order Bfell can take a year
I will use AutoDefault Object to show it
I will use RepairGateSuite and build the same model as the first demo
After running L2 Default Check, I will have a successful result, one of the total number is one of my modules.
After that, I will go to the Steps, Review guest source, Fail here, for the module to be failed.
Then I will go to the next step, Review failed module.
After that, I will go to the next step, Review failed module.
I will see the detailed results in the module info file.
I will open this file and I will see that
This is the result of my
here
Yes, it will have success for one
this module
Yes, you will not see a response of 100
percent
I will go to say it is 88 percent
So that's the end of my demo for the options for using Tool Contact Automation to find delta of unit test modules.
Thank you for watching my demo.